Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
5/74-1. This is Dispatch. Receiving?
This is 5/74-1.
-Location?
-Neukölln. close to railway station.
Pregnancy complications.
Lipschitzallee Ecke Kölner Damm.
On our way.
And could you take
the late shift tomorrow?
A colleague has a family emergency.
Sorry. can't do it. Next time. OK?
Are you sure?
I've been phoning around for an hour.
Sorry. I've also got a family emergency.
It's ok. I will work it out somehow.
-Nothing serious. I hope?
-I have to go to Austria.
Austria? I didn't know
you had family there.
Neither did I. until recently.
-My father died.
-Sorry to hear that.
It's fine. I didn't know him.
My biological father. I mean.
And now I've inherited his house.
It's fine. we're here.
You'll be fine.
-Take me to hospital. Please.
-OK. let's get you to the ambulance.
Stop. stop. stop! The baby's coming!
Quick. blankets!
Everything's fine. Just lie down.
I can see the head.
Let's work together.
When I say push. push.
Now push - hard.
Again. with all your strength. Push!
You're doing great.
Another big push. Great.
The head's out.
Take a deep breath.
Here she comes. She's here!
Hello. little one.
THE RED STAG INN
7 HR 48 MIN 726 KM FASTEST ROUTE
Busy night?
Good morning baby!
Morning.
Sleep well?
Well enough.
I've packed everything
except your toilet stuff.
Nervous?
We don't have to go there.
We could fix all the stuff from here.
No. we're definitely going.
- Did you water the plants?
- Yes.
- Are all the windows closed?
Are you sure this is the right place?
They cancelled the booking.
Seriously!
This is shit.
What now?
No idea.
Let's just go to the house.
Maybe that woman who's taking
care of everything is there.
Your destination is on the left.
Holy shit.
SURGERY DR. EDUARD SARSTEINER
GENERAL PRACTITIONER
Judith?
Yes?
You won't remember me. I'm Paula.
You can call me Auntie Paula.
just like you used to.
Welcome home. Judith.
I'm Ryan.
- Judith's husband.
- Hello. Ryan.
Come on in. Moni! They're here!
We have prepared a room for you.
I hope that's fine.
That's fine.
- Right?
- Yes.
Hello! We can keep it informal. right?
After all.
I knew you when you were this big.
This is Monika. Ms. Ramsauer.
She's been helping out.
It's so nice that you're back.
Even if it is a sad occasion.
Anyway. never mind.
I'll let you settle in.
Let me know if you need
help with anything.
And that goes for you two. too. Bye.
Yes. and there's some food in the oven.
I made something vegetarian.
Can't be too careful these days.
Come on. I'll show you to your room.
How was the trip?
Did everything go smoothly?
Yes. it was fine.
Do you want to see the house now.
or shall we wait for daylight?
Tomorrow will be fine. The real
estate agent isn't coming until noon.
Eduard. your father...
He would certainly have wanted
the house to stay in the family.
Then he should have taken
care of his daughter.
You keep talking about my father.
There's no mother?
Just get settled in.
You must be tired after the long drive.
Maybe she's still running
around this dump somewhere.
Judith. she's dead.
She died a long time ago.
I'm sure you have a lot of questions
and I will try to answer them for you.
When the time is right.
Reception is terrible here.
but there is a landline
and my number's on the kitchen table.
This place...
Keeps going.
Thanks!
Cheers.
Is that your father?
Maybe.
Interesting guy.
I mean...
Who were these people?
They live in a house like this.
then abandon their only child?
Money can't have been an issue.
I always thought my mother might
have been a junkie... or a minor.
That she had to give me up.
Would you have preferred that?
It would make it easier.
Is everything OK?
Yes.
How much do you think this
place is worth? Altogether?
I don't know. It needs a lot of work.
And the area is hardly booming.
You won't get rich.
- But I love you anyway.
- Thanks.
Do you actually have to accept
an inheritance?
No idea.
But there are no debts.
so you would make some money.
And what would you do with all that money?
I'm happy when you're happy.
- Morning. Baby.
- Morning.
Your room?
No idea.
Sleep well?
Yes... Like a stone.
- What are those pills?
- Antidepressants and antipsychotics.
Are they taken together?
For some mental health conditions.
Schizophrenia. for example.
I can develop this in Berlin.
Good morning. Sorry to disturb you.
Doctor. It's an emergency.
You are a doctor?
Yes. I am.
But can't you call an ambulance?
No. The nearest hospital is an hour away.
My mother has chronic pain.
What is she taking?
Oxycodone. Your father has some
in the medicine cabinet.
- How long has she been taking it?
- I wouldn't be here if it wasn't urgent.
Hold on a moment. yeah?
What's up?
I have to go out. It's an Emergency.
Emergency?
Yes. an emergency.
The real estate agent arrives at eleven.
Can you get the photos done by then?
Yes. sure.
Thank you for coming.
My name is Franz Scheichl.
Your father always looked after my mother.
Without him. she'd be long gone.
What was my father like?
A great doctor.
And a good hunter.
That's it?
Mum?
Mum. the doctor's here.
Mrs. Scheichl? I'll just give you
a quick examination. alright?
Judith?
I'm scared.
You don't have to be scared.
What's it like over there?
On the other side?
You've been there.
What did your mother mean?
She often talks nonsense.
Especially when she's in pain.
Did you actually know me?
As a child. I mean.
Yes. I did.
And? What was I like?
Just a child. You ran around.
you played. you cried. That's it.
Why did my parents give me up?
You just disappeared one day.
And my mother?
Did she also just "disappear"?
Yes.
-Did no one find that strange?
-Look. people talk a lot of crap.
I helped you. so now it's your turn.
People say that. out here. everybody
knows everybody else's business.
But that's not true.
Who is this?
Hanna Schatzenberger.
She was a friend of your mother's.
Where can I find her?
I'll give you the address.
It's some way out of town.
What the...
- Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
- It's fine.
Here's a little welcome present.
Thanks. that wouldn't have been necessary.
May I take a look?
These pictures aren't great.
I don't know what happened.
Well. you're a professional.
You'll sort it out.
Sure.
Maybe the house just doesn't
want to be photographed.
Do you actually enjoy it?
Shooting weddings?
You used to work in advertising.
didn't you?
Until the work dried up.
Right?
May I be a little indiscreet?
How long have you been married?
- Three years.
- And where did you meet?
At the cinema.
During French Film Week.
Both Francophiles.
Oui. oui. la la.
And how is the family planning going?
I mean. nobody is getting any younger.
No plans at all.
You could make a fresh start here.
There are lots of weddings
out here in the countryside
and it's a great place for children.
What's that African saying?
"It takes a village to raise a child."
I'm really embarrassed.
I don't usually get lost.
It's very easy to do here.
But why are you soaked?
I stumbled on the shore
and ended up in the lake.
It's nice to have you back. Doctor.
I'm Susi Loidl.
Another aunt?
Practically.
I own the dog grooming service here.
You look great.
You're going to stay here with us. right?
It's such a wonderful place for children.
Wouldn't it be great if there
was a child here again?
We are perfectly happy without children.
A lovely woman like you without children?
- We can't have that!
- I like my life just fine the way it is.
You've still got time...
A little. at least.
- Right. Susi?
- Right.
Thank you.
See you next week.
- What's happening next week?
- I have an appointment.
- At your doctor's office.
- Yes. me too... A check-up.
- We'll be back in Berlin next week.
- Dear.
We'll see.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye. Doctor.
Ryan!
Don't open the door!
What are you doing down there?
Wait. One second.
Sorry. baby. I was developing negatives.
- What took you so long?
- I got lost.
- You did?
- Yeah. me.
Something's wrong with my camera.
Then I found this one...
A fucking Nikon F4.
The darkroom still works.
Even the chemicals are fine.
I can develop the images here.
Do you think that's her?
I always wanted to get to know my mother.
I'll finish up here.
And then you'll finally
get to know her. OK?
I'm going to have a bath first.
By the way. the realtor was here.
Shit. sorry.
She'll come back tomorrow.
Judith!
Judith?
Hey. hey. hey.
Komm. Hey. hey.
It felt so real.
Like I was drowning.
- Morning. Baby.
- Morning.
- Sleep well?
- Yes. really well.
You made quite a lot of noise.
During sex?
Sleeping.
Is it worse than yesterday?
What do you mean?
- You want to see a doctor?
- Why should I see a doctor?
You've been sick three days in a row.
Judith. you have visitors.
Who is it?
- Good morning. Doctor.
- Good morning.
Morning.
I'm sorry.
but I'm not a practicing doctor.
You helped Scheichl's mother last week.
You wouldn't send us away. would you?
Look. Mrs. Scheichl was an emergency.
If I don't get my examination.
I'll end up an emergency.
Doctor. please. We need you.
Hanna Schatzenberger.
She was a friend of your mother's.
I have to go out for a while.
Has the real estate agent been in touch?
- Are you kidding?
- No... Why?
You cancelled the appointment.
We argued about it.
What?
You wanted to rethink the whole thing?
Stop messing around.
I cancelled a fucking job in Berlin
because you insisted on staying here.
Stop bullshit!
GEBETSROITHER REAL ESTATE AGENT
JOHANNA GEBETSROITHER
Voicemail Gebethsroither.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Hello. this is Judith Scholten.
Please call me back. It's urgent.
I have to...
Ryan!
Ryan?
- Hey. is everything...
- Leave me alone.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Okay.
- I'm just tired.
After all. I have to deal
with everything round here.
Right. And what exactly have you done?
Develop a few pictures?
Did you fuck those up like
the ones of the house?
You rethink the whole thing...
we argued about it...
Sick for three days....
Cancelled the appointment...
You helped Scheichl's mother last week...
Ms. Schatzenberger?
I am the daughter of Anna
and Eduard Sarsteiner.
I would like to talk
to you about my mother.
You were friends.
What happened to her?
Why did my mother give me up?
Was she sick?
They will take your child.
I don't have a child.
And I don't want one.
You have to be stronger than your mother.
Hanna? Are you here?
Go!
Get out!
Hanna.
Hanna?
Hanna dear...
You can't keep running away.
They look after you at the group home.
Come on. Hanna.
You have to take your pills.
Otherwise you'll feel awful again.
What is it with you and this old shack?
There you go. take your pills.
They'll calm you down.
Are you crazy? That's enough!
Give us a hand here!
Get over here and help!
Fuck!
Have you got a cigarette for me?
Can you take me to a pharmacy?
Greetings. Doctor.
- Do we know each other?
- We haven't met before.
- Do you need a towel?
- The morning-after pill. please.
It's too late for that.
Excuse me?
No charge. It's going to be a girl.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Judith is wonderful... Isn't she?
You should never have wasted
that money on your vasectomy.
- Excuse me?
- Vasectomy.
Snip. snip.
Snip... snip...
The women in this village
have always been special.
As long as they know what they have to do.
No need to be afraid. young man.
Wait...
I've got something for you.
- What is it?
- From Hanna.
Thanks.
Take care of yourself.
Judith!
Is everything OK?
Yes.
Where have you been?
- Judith!
- Yes! Fuck. I'll be right there!
Are you going to tell me
where you've been?
Just out.
What's that?
This is my childhood.
My mother almost let me
drown when I was four.
The freezing lake water saved my life.
I...
I was dead. but my body was so cold
that my brain wasn't damaged.
Although I'm not so sure about that.
What do you mean?
Well. that I don't have brain damage.
MEDICAL REPORT DISCHARGE LETTER
JUDITH SARSTEINER
How messed up do you have to be to let
your own child drown?
We have to get out of here.
This house is making us sick.
The house?
Because it's my house.
it's making you sick?
At first you didn't want to stay at all.
- Now you're...
- What?
I don't know. You're...
Not yourself anymore.
Maybe I'm just like my mother.
Maybe I'm completely insane.
- You're not like your mother.
- How would you know?
You don't know me at all.
What's it like over there?
On the other side?
You've been there...
Thanks.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Come here.
Morning. baby.
Did I wake you? I'm almost finished.
How long have I been asleep?
Since yesterday afternoon. Like an angel.
What day is it today?
Tuesday. right?
It's Friday today.
What month?
- Seriously?
- Yes!
- Seriously.
- July.
- Are you not feeling well?
- I'm fine.
- Everything's fine. Thanks.
- Are you sure?
Yes.
- Is everything alright?
- Yes!
Why did you lock the door?
Can I get a little privacy
in this fucking house?
- Sorry. I just wanted to check...
- Now you've checked. Well?
Have I done something wrong?
- I want to go home.
- You are home!
No. to Berlin.
I want to go back to Berlin.
But we gave up the apartment in Berlin.
You begged me to stay here.
We made the decision together.
We decided that?
- I didn't decide anything.
-You wanted our child.
- Our child?
- Yes. our child.
I don't want that.
I don't want this fucking kid!
- Baby. calm down...
- Don't tell me to calm down.
Who are you really?
Cleaning cars. trimming hedges back
to the fucking Fifties?
Did you lie to me? About your vasectomy?
You tricked me into getting pregnant.
I don't know what this thing
in my belly is. but I don't want it!
- You have to stop fighting it.
- Let go of me.
Paula can help you.
- Paula. Of course.
- Please. You can't mess this up.
- Stop it!
- You can do this. We can do it!
- Let go of me.
- For us.
- You're hurting me.
- For the child.
Let go. you're hurting me!
Good morning.
I brought some breakfast.
You have to eat something.
Come on.
And you. clean up this mess.
Be careful.
Look out.
Come on. eat.
Do you like it?
I baked it myself.
Everything will be fine.
Just the way it should be.
Have you cleaned up?
Then heat the milk.
Your mum always drank warm
milk when she didn't feel well.
- Can I ask you something. Auntie Paula?
- Of course! You can ask me anything.
What really happened to my mum?
Your mum...
Your mother wasn't up to the task.
She tried to do something to you.
And then...
Then what?
Then she killed herself.
Your dad thought your mum
wasn't quite right in the head.
She heard voices.
But it wasn't her imagination.
Don't fight it.
You've been away for a long time...
But this place... this house...
Your family... have always been with you.
You may have thought
that you'd been abandoned...
But you were never alone.
Something for the stomach ache.
Get some rest.
They mean well.
Mr. Scheichl?
My boy's not here.
if you're looking for him.
It's so good that you're back.
It's good for everyone.
Including me.
I'm going to wear this.
To the celebration.
My mother wore it and so did
my grandmother.
We've been waiting for this for so long.
Stop fighting it. Judith. It's pointless.
Your mum almost brought
disaster upon us...
But now everything
is the way it should be again.
There must always be something
holding the heavens in place.
Your mother tried to spare you.
Now it is your child's turn.
We all have to make sacrifices.
Otherwise the world falls apart.
Hey. baby.
Are you hungry?
It's such a lovely place now.
You must be glad
you didn't sell it. right?
I want to go home.
You are home.
Everybody who loves you is here.
Everything's great.
Now it's lying just right.
It won't be long now.
You need to drink more. You're dehydrated.
You have to make sure
she has enough water.
Rest. Judith.
We don't want you to suffer
the same fate as your mum.
Rest.
I can feel her.
They will take your child.
You have to be stronger than your mother.
Come. Come with me.
Wait here.
I have to go out for a while.
Stay down.
Don't run away. baby.
You have to be stronger than your mother.
Come on.
Let what is in the past
Remain in the past.
Carve your own paths
But never alone.
Let what hurt you
Be forgotten
Never give up
And never give in
You still have time.
Just try to be free.
Let what is in the past
Remain in the past.
Between then. today and the future
Lies an hour: the present.
It is the new. born from mourning.
Shaped from fear.
It wakes in the light
Cast the memories far from yourself.
Never think of yesterday.
But let tomorrow be what it will.
It lives within you...
All that has passed.
Subtitling: FAST TITLES MEDIA
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-